<!--
strings.xml
This is where we create the strings that are needed for use in the app.
Created by: Jordan Graves
Created on: 2/13/19
Last Modified by: Jordan Graves
Last Modified on: 3/1/2019
Assignment/Project: A290 Android Development Final Project
-->
<resources>
    <string name="AppName">Game Blitz</string>
    <string name="SudokuName">Sudoku Blitz</string>
    <string name="TicTacToeName">TicTacToe Blitz</string>
    <string name="ChessName">Chess Blitz</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="MainMenuSudoku">Sudoku</string>
    <string name="MainMenuTicTacToe">TicTacToe</string>
    <string name="MainMenuChess">Chess</string>
    <string name="MainMenuAbout">About</string>
    <string name="MainMenuExit">Exit</string>
    <string name="SudokuMenuNewGame">New Game</string>
    <string name="SudokuMenuAbout">About</string>
    <string name="SudokuMenuMainMenu">Main Menu</string>
    <string name="SudokuMenuExit">Exit</string>
    <string name="TicTacToeMenuNewGame">New Game</string>
    <string name="TicTacToeMenuAbout">About</string>
    <string name="TicTacToeMenuMainMenu">Main Menu</string>
    <string name="TicTacToeMenuExit">Exit</string>
    <string name="ChessMenuNewGame">New Game</string>
    <string name="ChessMenuAbout">About</string>
    <string name="ChessMenuMainMenu">Main Menu</string>
    <string name="ChessMenuExit">Exit</string>
    <string name="MainMenuAboutText">In this app you will find three games in which you will be
    asked to complete the games before exiting the app or you will lose all progress. We made the
    app this way to be devoted to the people around the world who enjoy challenges of completing
    games in one sitting and we hope that we have accomplished this. If there are any issues with
    the app please contact the main developer at Jordang3177@gmail.com</string>
    <string name="AboutName">About Game Blitz</string>
    <string name="SudokuAboutText">In this part of the app you will find the Sudoku portion of the
    app. Sudoku is a 9x9 game in which you have to complete the board, and each row, column, and box
    cannot have the same number in any of the three. Once you meet all these requirements and
    the board is filled then you have won the game!</string>
    <string name="SudokuAboutName">About Sudoku Blitz</string>
    <string name="SudokuGameTitle">Difficulty</string>
    <string name="SudokuEasyLabel">Easy</string>
    <string name="SudokuMediumLabel">Medium</string>
    <string name="SudokuHardLabel">Hard</string>
    <string name="TicTacToeAboutText">In this part of the app you will find the TicTacToe portion of the app.
    TicTacToe is a game played on a 3x3 board where you need to get three of your pieces in a row
    there are traditionally two players, one for the x, and one for the os. Players rotate each turn
    and the game either ends when one person has three of their tokens in 3 of a row, or when the
    board is filled which results in a draw.</string>
    <string name="ChessAboutText">In this part of the app you will find the Chess portion of the app.
    Chess is a game in which two players try to defeat the other by taking out their king while
    protecting their own. You have a multitude of pieces each with their own movement rules.
    The pawn which can move either 1 space or 2 spaces forward on the first move, and may only
    take an opposing piece if it is diagonal to it and if it ever reaches the other side of the board
    then it will become one of the pieces you have lost. The rook which can move in straight lines.
    The Bishop which can move in diagonal lines. The knight which can move in an L shape.
    The Queen which can move any direction. The King which can move in any direction but only 1 space
    at a time.</string>
    <string name="CannotDo">Cannot do this</string>
    <string name="SudokuKeypadTitle">Sudoku KeyPad</string>
    <string name="SizeOfBoard">3</string>
    <string name="X">"   X   "</string>
    <string name="O">"   O   "</string>
    <string name="none">"          "</string>
    <string name="TicTacToeContinueScreenLabel">Want to play TicTacToe? Click here!</string>
    <string name="TicTacToeResetGame">Reset Game</string>
    <string name="ChessContinueScreenLabel">Want to play Chess? Click here!</string>
    <string name="ChessCellWidthSize">35dp</string>
    <string name="TicTacToeBackButton">Back to Menu</string>

</resources>
